A Finding Aid to the Fidel Danieli papers, 1962-1987, in the Archives of American Art AAA.danifide
Archives of American Art
- Printed Material, 1969-1985; Series 3; 2.1 Linear feet Boxes 7-9
  - Artists, 1969-1982; 3.1
    - S - Judith Simonian, Barbara Smith, Jean St. Pierre, 1976-1982 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - S-T - Joynn Suzar, Masami Teraoka, Michael Todd, 1975-1981 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - T-V - Joyce Treiman, De Wain Valentine, Judith Von Euer, 1971-1981 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - W - Gordon Wagner, Doug Wheeler, Guy Williams, 1970-1982 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - W - Jay Willis, Michael Wingo, Tom Wudl, 1976-1980 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Y - Rita Yokoi, Richard Yokomi, Nancy Youdelman, 1975-1981 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Z - Connie Zehr, Elynn Zimmerman, 1976-1978 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Group Shows, 1977-1981 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Performances, 1972-1982 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Los Angeles Galleries and Art Venues, 1971-1982; 3.2
    This subseries consists of exhibition announcements from various Los Angeles galleries and art venues.
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically by gallery name.
    - A - ACE, Adrienne Simard, Anhalt/Barnes, 1976-1982 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - A - Art Space, Artworks, Asher/Faure, 1979-1982 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - B - Bernard Jacobson, Broxton, Bryon Weber, 1976-1981 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - C - Charles Cowles, China Club, Cirrus, 1976-1982 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - C-E - Claire Copley, David Stuart, Ellie Blankfort, 1976-1978 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - F - Ferus, Floating Wall, Foundation for Art Resources, 1976-1980 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - G-H - Gallery West, Gemini G.E.L., Herbert Palmer, 1979-1982 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - H-J - Hunsaker/Schlesinger, Irving Blum, Jacqueline Anhalt, 1971-1982 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - J - James Corcoran, Jan Baum, Jancar/Kuhlenshmidt, 1977-1982 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Janus Gallery, 1976-1981 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - K-L - Kirk de Gooyer, L.A.C.E., L. A. Louver, 1976-1981 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - L - Landau/Alexander, Larry Gagosian, Leopold/Gold, 1979-1982 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - L-M - Los Angeles Museum of Art, Malinda Wyatt, Margo Leavin, 1978-1982 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - M - Meghan Williams, Mirage, Mizuno, 1978-1982 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - M-N - Molly Barnes, Museum of Contemporary Art, Neil G. Ovsey, 1978-1982 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - N-O - Newspace, Nicholas Wilder, Oranges/Sardines, 1976-1982 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - R - Re:vision, Roger Wong, Ron Salgado, 1976-1982 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - R - Rosamund Felsen, Roy Boyd, Ruth S. Schaffner, 1976-1982 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - S - Sanguine Suite, Simard Weber, Some Serious Business, 1977-1981 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - S - Space, Stella Polaris, Swope, 1976-1982 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - T-V - Thomas Lewallen, Tortue, Ulrike Kantor, Vanguard, 1976-1982 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - California Museums and University Galleries, 1976-1982; 3.3
    The bulk of this subseries consists of exhibition announcements from museums as well as the galleries and exhibition spaces at universities and colleges in California, not restricted to Los Angeles.
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically by the name of the museum or educational institution.
    - A - ARCO, Art Center College of Design, 1976-1982 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - B - Brand Library, Baxter Art Gallery, 1976-1981 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - C - California State Universities of Dominguez Hills, Fullerton, L.A., Northridge, 1976-1982 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - C-G - Cedars-Sinai Medical Center, Craft & Folk Art Museum, Downey Museum, Grossmont College, 1976-1981 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - L - Long Beach Museum of Art, Los Angeles County Museum of Art, 1976-1978 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - M - Mount St. Mary's College, Mount San Antonio College Gallery, 1978-1982 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Municipal Art Gallery, 1977-1982 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - M-N - Museum of Contemporary Art in Los Angeles, Newport Harbor Art Museum, 1976-1980 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - O-P - Otis Art Institute, Palomar College, Pasadena City College, Pierce College, 1976-1982 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - S-U - San Diego State University, University of California Irvine, University of California Los Angeles, 1976-1982 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - U - University of California San Diego Mandeville Gallery, University of California Santa Barbara, 1978-1982 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Other Printed Material, 1970-1985; 3.4
    This subseries consists of assorted printed material such as exhibition announcements, magazines, press releases, and clippings.
    The first two folders of exhibition announcements and auctions retained their original headings which groups the material by event type, the remainder of the printed material is organized by document type.
    - Concerts and Events, 1973-1977 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Auctions and Benefits, 1970-1982 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Journal 40th Issue, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Images and Issues, 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - News Clippings, 1979-1983 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 10)